zteusa.com 2018-04-18

# Privacy Policy - ZTE USA

#### Privacy Policy

The privacy policy set forth below (the "Privacy Policy") applies to online services ([www.zteusa.com](http://www.zteusa.com/)) directly provided by ZTE USA Inc. (herein after referred to as “ZTE” and the services referred to as the "ZTE Service") .ZTE is committed to protecting the online privacy of visitors, users and customers of all of ZTE Services.

As you use our services, the purpose of this Privacy Policy is to indicate you clearly how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy, typically: • What kind of information we gather about you when you visit or submit information to a ZTE Service; • How we may use that information, and • How we may disclose the collected information to third parties.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to Personal Information that you provide directly to third parties whose services or content you access via a ZTE Service. You should check the applicable privacy policy of any third party service providers whose service or content you access.

To the extent permitted by law, ZTE does not represent or warrant that ZTE Services, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any specific jurisdiction. Those who choose to access ZTE Service do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.

1\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

We may collect your personal information through the way of your applying and registering a ZTE USA Website accountant. We may combine the information we collect from you with information obtained from other sources to help us improve its overall accuracy and completeness, and to help us better tailor our interactions with you. In addition, we may also collect information relating to your use of our Web sites through the use of various technologies, including cookies.

(1)Personal Information

At various locations on our online Service, such as ID creation, in registration forms, surveys, and polls, registration of your products, a purchase a product, download a software update, or use our [Internet@TV](mailto:Internet@TV)content service, we may request that you supply us with Personal Information, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, home or work telephone number contact preferences, and credit card information, your name, e-mail address, mailing address (hereafter Personal Information ) . You will know when we are collecting Personal Information, because ZTE attempts to collect Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit it to us through our online

personal accountant registration. Although you do not have to provide us with any information to use ZTE Service, you may not be able to fully utilize all of ZTE Service if you choose not to provide certain information. If you do choose to give us Personal Information through ZTE Service, we will collect and retain that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

ZTE takes reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on you to update or correct your Personal Information whenever necessary. All users of ZTE Service are required to provide true, current, complete and accurate Personal Information when prompted.

(2)Cookies

At times, we may use a feature of your browser to send your computer a "cookie". Cookies are used by thousands of web sites in order to enhance your web experience. A cookie is a small data file that assigns a unique anonymous number to your browser from a web server and is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can not damage or read information stored on your hard drive. Cookies make your web experience more enjoyable by storing passwords and preferences. You can adjust your browser settings to refuse all cookies or to inform you when a cookie is being placed on your hard drive. However, your election not to accept cookies may diminish your experience with the Site because of additional time needed to repeatedly enter information.

(3)Non-Personal Information

When you use a ZTE Service, we may also collect "non-personal information". We consider "non-personal information" to be information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you personally, such as demographic information (education level, profession, zip code, etc.) , technical information, such as your IP address and other anonymous data involving your use of ZTE Service. Non- personal information may also include information that you provide us through your use of ZTE Service, such as the terms you enter into the search functions of ZTE Service. We reserve the right to use or disclose non-personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy.

2\. USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use your Personal Information to provide you with any services that you may request or require, to communicate with you and to allow you to participate in online surveys. We may use aggregated non-personal information about our users to understand our website's demographics, such as the geographic distribution of our users, the number of users visiting a certain location, a combination of these and/or other demographics. We may also use the personal or non-personal information we collect to analyze how ZTE Service is being used, and to improve the content of ZTE Service, and for marketing and promotional efforts so that we or any of our related companies can send you information about products and services which we believe may be of interest to you.

If you send us an e-mail with questions or comments, we may use your Personal Information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference.

In all, we may also use your personal information so as to: • To fulfill your requests by us or by others involved in fulfillment. • To contact you for customer satisfaction surveys, market research or in connection with certain transactions. • To support products or services you have obtained from us. • To personalize your experience while you are on our sites, make navigation easier, and for Web site usage statistics.

3\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES (1)Aggregate Information

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with any non-affiliated third party without your permission. We may disclose aggregate information, such as demographic information, and our statistical analyses to third parties, including advertisers or other business partners. This aggregate information does not include your Personal Information .

(2)Service Providers

We sometimes engage unaffiliated businesses to assist us in providing you certain services. For example, we may use third parties (including a payment gateway service provider) to provide advertising, marketing and promotional assistance, provide e-mail services, or facilitate sales and our online services. In those instances, we may need to share your Personal Information with them. We require these companies to use your Personal Information only to provide the particular product or service and do not authorize them to use your Personal Information for any other reason.

We sometimes offer promotions in conjunction with a third party sponsor. If you choose to participate in one of those promotions, we may share your information with the sponsor if they need it to send you a product or other special promotion they offer.

(3)Business Transactions Involving ZTE Service

As ZTE Service continues to develop, we may engage in commercial transactions such as buying, selling or combination of such with other businesses. If so, non- personal and Personal Information that we or other businesses have collected will likely be transferred as part of the transaction. If we engage in such a business, we will attempt to ensure that requests made to us regarding e-mail communications will be honored by relevant third parties.

(4)Third Party Advertisers

We may use third-party advertising companies to deliver specific advertisements to you. These companies would collect non-personal information about your visits to ZTE Service in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may also aggregate your non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research, and other similar purposes. These companies may place their own cookies on your computer. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting and using this information, you may visit each third-party advertiser's website directly and opt-out.

(5)Other Disclosures

We may disclose Personal Information when we are required or requested in good faith to do so by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; to enforce or apply our rights and agreements; or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of ZTE Service and ZTE, our users, or others.

4\. SECURITY OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your Personal Information. However, please remember that there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically prior to our collection. The Personal Information we collect is stored within databases that we control. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. We restrict access to Personal Information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

5\. ARCHIVED INFORMATION

We maintain archives of its web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database. We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

6\. ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy, the accuracy of your Personal Information or the use of your Personal Information , or any requests to access your information or that we correct, update, or remove your information in our databases, should be directed via e-mail for general media inquiries to: [media@zteusa.com](mailto:media@zteusa.com).

For general media inquiries to: [media@zteusa.com](mailto:media@zteusa.com).

Or via regular mail to:

ZTE USA Inc.

2425 N. Central Expressway, Suite 800 

Richardson, TX 75080

Or via Phone: (972) 671-8885

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is ZTE’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between ZTE and you.

If we receive a request to change your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your Personal Information stored in databases we actively use to operate ZTE Service will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable.

However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information removed from, or changed in, our active ZTE Service databases. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our End User Terms and Conditions for the Application. In addition, it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 26, 2012, and complies with ZTE’s Corporate Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and will post any material changes to this Privacy Policy as soon as they go into effect. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

This privacy policy was last updated on December, 2012.
